[
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "You’ve learned about the small “や,” “ゆ,” and “よ” and what happens when you combine them with the basic consonant sounds in hiragana. Test your knowledge and take a quiz! First, let’s recap:"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "K and S",
    "options": [
      "Kya – きゃ",
      "Kyu – きゅ",
      "Kyo – きょ",
      "Sha – しゃ",
      "Shu – しゅ",
      "Sho – しょ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "C and N",
    "options": [
      "Cha – ちゃ",
      "Chu – ちゅ",
      "Cho – ちょ",
      "Nya – にゃ",
      "Nyu – にゅ",
      "Nyo – にょ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "H, M, and R",
    "options": [
      "Hya – ひゃ",
      "Hyu – ひゅ",
      "Hyo – ひょ",
      "Myi – みぃ",
      "Myu – みゅ",
      "Myo – みょ",
      "Rya – りゃ",
      "Ryu – りゅ",
      "Ryo – りょ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Kya",
    "options": ["きゃ", "きょ", "きゅ"],
    "answer": "きゃ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Sho",
    "options": ["しゃ", "しょ", "しゅ"],
    "answer": "しょ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Cha",
    "options": ["ちょ", "ちゃ", "ちゅ"],
    "answer": "ちゃ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Hya",
    "options": ["ひょ", "ひゅ", "ひゃ"],
    "answer": "ひゃ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Myu",
    "options": ["みゅ", "みょ", "みゃ"],
    "answer": "みゅ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Ryo",
    "options": ["りゃ", "りょ", "りゅ"],
    "answer": "りょ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Kyo",
    "options": ["きゃ", "きゅ", "きょ"],
    "answer": "きょ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Sha",
    "options": ["しょ", "しゃ", "しゅ"],
    "answer": "しゃ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Cho",
    "options": ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ", "ちょ"],
    "answer": "ちょ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Hyu",
    "options": ["ひゅ", "ひゃ", "ひょ"],
    "answer": "ひゅ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Mya",
    "options": ["みょ", "みゅ", "みゃ"],
    "answer": "みゃ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Rya",
    "options": ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ"],
    "answer": "りゃ"
  },
  {"type": "mc", "prompt": "Chu", "options": ["ちょ", "ちゃ", "ちゅ"], "answer": "ちゅ"}
]